bestmark.com 2019-09-07

# BestMark - Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for BestMark. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your personal information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

BestMark’s website uses cookies provide users secure login to our website. Use of cookies does not allow BestMark to gather personal information from your computer or mobile device. BestMark does not share or sell information about user behaviors and preferences to third parties, except to provide survey response data to our clients. Surveys submitted to clients do not include personal identifying information of the user who submitted the survey, unless the user enters such information in survey responses.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

BestMark’s systems are proprietary and run on our own servers. Personal data stored in BestMark’s systems are not accessible to service providers such as hosting providers.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 952-922-3890 or via email.
